A Guide to the Sol and Virginia Wrenn family papers, 1815-2020
Library of Virginia
- Virginia Wrenn Papers, 1921-2017., Extent: 5 boxes. (Box 21-25)
  - Writing, story-telling, and poetry, 1973-2013., 3 boxes (Box 22-24)
    - Jolly Wrenn Bards programs, (1974-1975)-(1978-1979) (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - Jolly Wrenn Bards programs, (1980-1981)-(1985-1986) (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - Jolly Wrenn Bards programs, (1986-1987)-(1990-1991) (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - Jolly Wrenn Bards reports, 1986-1989 (Box 23, Folder 4)
    - Jolly Wrenn Bards history, 1991 (see also box 37) (Box 23, Folder 5)
    - Jolly Wrenn Bards--Under the Mushroom Tree, by Ginny Wrenn (Box 23, Folder 6)
    - National Storytellers League--Story Art magazine, 2012-2013 (Box 23, Folder 7)
    - 50 Tellable Tales from Story Art Magazine (Box 23, Folder 8)
    - International Society of Poets certificate, awards, 1996 (see box 39) (Box 23, Folder 9)
    - International Society of Poets convention photographs, 1996 (includes photographs of visit with relatives) (Box 23, Folder 10)
    - Poetry Society of Virginia membership directory, 2002 (Box 23, Folder 11)
    - Crestwood Elementary School book chat, 1985 (Box 23, Folder 12)
    - Crestwood Elementary School writers conference, 1985 (Box 23, Folder 13)
    - Outside My Window Inside the Nest, by Virginia Wrenn, 2005 (Box 24, Folder 1)
    - Virginia Wrenn--ritings and stories (Box 24, Folder 2)
    - Virginia Wrenn--poetry (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - Virginia Wrenn--haikus (see also box 38) (Box 24, Folder 4)
    - Creative poetry forms (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Crestwood Farms Garden Club and gardening, 1963-2015., 1 box (Box 24)
    - Crestwood Farms Garden Club yearbook and directory, 2000-2001 (Box 24, Folder 6)
    - Crestwood Farms Garden Club yearbook, 2014-2015 (Box 24, Folder 7)
    - Crestwood Farms Garden Club shows and events, 1963, 1964, 1995 (Box 24, Folder 8)
    - Crestwood Farms Garden Club Forty Years of Memories anniversary show, 1996 (Box 24, Folder 9)
    - Crestwood Farms Garden Club papers, 1979-1996 (Box 24, Folder 10)
    - Crestwood Farms Garden Club Piedmont District awards papers, 1994-1996 (Box 24, Folder 11)
    - Crestwood Farms Garden Club SAR 8 Horticulture Achievement Award, Piedmont District, 2001 (Box 24, Folder 12)
    - Virginia Federation of Garden Clubs convention, 1989 (Box 24, Folder 13)
    - Piedmont District, Virginia Federation of Garden Clubs Celebrate Freedom flower show, 1991 (Box 24, Folder 14)
    - Maymont flower and garden show, 1991 (Box 24, Folder 15)
    - Southside Plaza (South of the James Garden Clubs) flower shows, 1978-1984 (Box 24, Folder 16)
    - South of the James Garden Clubs flower shows, 1989, 1991, 1993 (Box 24, Folder 17)
    - Tuckahoe Community Garden Clubs flower show, 1978 (Box 24, Folder 18)
    - Crestwood Farms Garden Club miscellanous papers, 1980-1996, undated (Box 24, Folder 19)
    - Crestwood Farms Garden Club photographs (Box 24, Folder 20)
    - Crestwood Farms Garden Club exhibit tags, 1993-1996, undated (Box 24, Folder 21)
    - Virginia Wrenn article on flowers and gardening through the years, 1980 (see also box 38) (Box 24, Folder 22)
    - Weddings and Flowers I've Planned scrapbook, 1977-1986 (see box 38) (Box 24, Folder 23)
  - Mrs. Virginia, 1956-1964, 1993-1994., 1 box (Box 25)
    - Mrs. Virginia scrapbook and ribbons, 1956 (see boxes 39 and 40) (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - Mrs. Virginia articles and papers, 1956-1964 (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - Mrs. America programs, 1956 (Box 25, Folder 3)
    - Mrs. America photographs, 1956 (Box 25, Folder 4)
    - Cypress Gardens postcards (Box 25, Folder 5)
    - Mrs. America correspondence, 1961 (Box 25, Folder 6)
    - Nation's Top Homemakers newsletters, 1961-1962 (Box 25, Folder 7)
    - Mrs. Virginia senior citizen pageant, 1993-1994 (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Miscellaneous, 1956-2010., 1 box (Box 25)
    - Card making (Box 25, Folder 9)
    - Card making design and calligraphy (Box 25, Folder 10)
    - A Practical Program to Achieve Economic Justice for Homemakers, October 1978-September 2008 (Box 25, Folder 11)
    - Recipes and Menus (Box 25, Folder 12)
    - Clippings, 1980-2010 (Box 25, Folder 13)
    - The Christmas Story: A Family Program for Christmas Eve (Box 25, Folder 14)
    - An Evening to Honor Christian Educators, 8 November 2007 (Box 25, Folder 15)
    - A Monarch's Journey by Judy Nickels (Box 25, Folder 16)
    - Flight 93 Memorial correspondence, 2015 (Box 25, Folder 17)
    - Miscellaneous correspondence, 1989, 2002, 2005 (Box 25, Folder 18)
    - Miscellaneous papers (see also boxes 31 and 38) (Box 25, Folder 19)
    - Certificates, 1956, 1985, 1999 (see also box 35, folder 7) (Box 25, Folder 20)
    - Quilt C.W.U. Jubilee photographs, 1991 (Box 25, Folder 21)
    - Photographs (see also box 43, folder 3) (Box 25, Folder 22)
- Wrenn Family Papers, 1907-2006., Extent: 2 boxes. (Box 26-27)
  Series IV: Wrenn Family Papers, 1815-2006, containing clippings, correspondence, diaries, genealogical notes, ledgers, lists, magazines, obituaries, photographs, wills, and other papers regarding Sol Wrenn, Sr. (1881-1960), Mary Cochran Wrenn (1889-1984), and Robert C. Wrenn (1931-). Papers highlight Sol Wrenn's service as Greensville County, Virginia, clerk of court and his political activities, as well as Robert Wrenn's service as clerk of court. Papers include genealogical notes on the Wrenn and related families, as well as a business ledger for Richelieu Moss of Sussex County, Virginia. Also includes miscellaneous ads, checks, postcards, promissory notes, receipts, and other papers.
  - Sol Wrenn, Sr. papers, 1914-1960., 2 boxes (Box 26-27)
    - Letters, 1914 (Box 26, Folder 1)
    - Letters, 1-2 August 1915 (Box 26, Folder 2)
    - Letters, 3-5 August 1915 (Box 26, Folder 3)
    - Letters, 6-9, undated August 1915 (Box 26, Folder 4)
    - Letters, before November 1917 (Box 26, Folder 5)
    - Letters, 1919 (Box 26, Folder 6)
    - Letters, 1921 (Box 26, Folder 7)
    - Letters, 1922 (Box 26, Folder 8)
    - Letters, July-November 1923 (Box 26, Folder 9)
    - Letters, December, undated 1923 (Box 26, Folder 10)
    - Letters, January 1924 (Box 26, Folder 11)
    - Letters, February-May 1924 (Box 26, Folder 12)
    - Letters, June-December, undated 1924 (Box 26, Folder 13)
    - Letters, July-August 1925 (Box 26, Folder 14)
    - Letters, September 1925 (Box 26, Folder 15)
    - Letters, October-November, undated 1925 (Box 26, Folder 16)
    - Letters, 1926 (Box 26, Folder 17)
    - Letters, Janury-May 1927 (Box 26, Folder 18)
    - Letters, June-September 1927 (Box 26, Folder 19)
    - Letters, October-December, undated 1927 (Box 26, Folder 20)
    - Letters, January 1928 (Box 26, Folder 21)
    - Letters, February-March 1928 (Box 26, Folder 22)
    - Letters April 1928 (Box 26, Folder 23)
    - Letters, May-June 1928 (Box 26, Folder 24)
    - Letters, July-December 1928 (Box 26, Folder 25)
    - Letters, January-February 1929 (Box 26, Folder 26)
    - Letters, March-June 1929 (Box 26, Folder 27)
    - Letters, July-August 1929 (Box 26, Folder 28)
    - Letters, September-December 1929 (Box 26, Folder 29)
    - Letters, January-July 1930 (Box 26, Folder 30)
    - Letters, August-December 1930 (Box 26, Folder 31)
    - Letters, January-May 1931 (Box 26, Folder 32)
    - Letters, June-September 1931 (Box 26, Folder 33)
    - Letters, January-May 1932 (Box 26, Folder 34)
    - Letters, June 1932 (Box 26, Folder 35)
    - Letters, 1-9 July 1932 (Box 27, Folder 1)
    - Letters, 11-14 July 1932 (Box 27, Folder 2)
    - Letters, 15-19 July 1932 (Box 27, Folder 3)
    - Letters, 21-28 July 1932 (Box 27, Folder 4)
    - Letters, August 1932 (Box 27, Folder 5)
    - Letters, September-December 1932 (Box 27, Folder 6)
    - Letters, 1933 (Box 27, Folder 7)
    - Letters, 1934 (Box 27, Folder 8)
    - Letters, 1935-1937 (Box 27, Folder 9)
    - Letters, 1940, 1945 (Box 27, Folder 10)
    - Letters, 1958-1959 (Box 27, Folder 11)
    - Death--letters and obituaries, February 1960 (Box 27, Folder 12)
    - Will, 8 September 1942 (Box 27, Folder 13)
    - Papers, 1926-1928, 1955, undated (Box 27, Folder 14)
    - Clippings, 1951, undated (Box 27, Folder 15)
    - Photographs, 1902, 1939, undated (Box 27, Folder 16)
  - Mary Cochran Wrenn papers, 1915-1984., 1 box (Box 27)
    - Diary, 1-8 August 1915 (Box 27, Folder 17)
    - Clippings and obituaries, 1965, 1984 (Box 27, Folder 18)
    - Correspondence, 1964, 1984 (see also box 31) (Box 27, Folder 19)
    - Furntiture--photographs and inventories, 1984[?] (Box 27, Folder 20)
  - Robert C. Wrenn papers, 1952-2006., 1 box (Box 27)
    - Greensville County clerk of court, 1967-2005 (Box 27, Folder 21)
    - Ruritans, 1978-2005 (Box 27, Folder 22)
    - Papers, 1952-2003 (Box 27, Folder 23)
    - Clippings, 1992-2006 (Box 27, Folder 24)
  - Wrenn family papers, 1815-1917., 1 box (Box 27)
    - Richelieu Moss ledger, ca. 1907-1917 (see box 32) (Box 27, Folder 25)
    - E. Moss Wrenn ration book, 1945 (Box 27, Folder 26)
    - Wrenn family genealogies (Box 27, Folder 27)
    - Miscellaneous family papers, 1815-1916 (see also box 35, folder 8) (Box 27, Folder 28)
- Wrenn Family Papers, 1907-2006., Extent: 2 boxes. (Box 26-27)
  Series V: Wimer Family Papers, 1894, 1907-1909, containing postcards, 1907-1909, to Millie Malcom (Wimer) (1890-1976) of Highland County, Virginia, containing family and social news, and the autograph book, 1893-1894, of Pricy Wimer (1884-1968) of Coffey County, Kansas.
  - Millie Malcom (Wimer) postcards, 1907-1909., 1 box (Box 27)
    - Postcards, 1907 (Box 27, Folder 29)
    - Postcards, 1908 (Box 27, Folder 30)
    - Postcards, 1909 (Box 27, Folder 31)
    - Postcards, undated (Box 27, Folder 32)
  - Pricy Wimer papers, 1893-1894., 1 box (Box 27)
    - Autograph book and clippings, 1893-1894, undated (Box 27, Folder 33)
- Oversized materials., Extent: 16 boxes. (Box 28-43)
  Oversized material is cross-referenced to the box and folder from which it was removed.
  - Riparian, Greensville County High School yearbook, 1935 (From box 12, folder 3) (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Riparian, Greensville County High School yearbook, 1936 (from box 12, folder 3) (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - The Yellow Jacket Randolph-Macon College yearbook, 1939 (from box 12, folder 10) (Box 28)
  - The Yellow Jacket Randolph-Macon College yearbook, 1940 (from box 12, folder 10) (Box 28)
  - The Hoist NavTraScol (Naval Training School) class book, July 1943 (from box 13, folder 10) (Box 28)
  - Inspirational Poems for Christian Homes by C. Clifford Hevener (from box 9, folder 4) (Box 29)
  - The Wilderness Road by Robert L. Kinkaid, 1947 (from box 21, folder 10) (Box 29)
  - What's Next, Pizarro? by Raymond and Kenneth Dyches, 1968 (from box 21, folder 10) (Box 29)
  - Win If You Can WRVA Radio show (3 records), 14 August 1950 (from box 2, folder 9) (Box 30)
  - Wrenn family Christmas--cassette (2), reel (2) tapes, 1963-1970 (from box 2, folder 11) (Box 31)
  - Sol and Ginny Wrenn 50th anniversary--cassette tape, 9 April 1999 (from box 2, folder 12) (Box 31)
  - Forest Hill Prebyterian Church, Dr. West's retirement--cassette tapes (3), 30 July 1995 (from box 5, folder 3) (Box 31)
  - Bon Air 1--cassette tape (from box 5, folder 17) (Box 31)
  - Bonsai--cassette tape, (from box 8, folder 12) (Box 31)
  - Ginny & Sol Belmont on Monument Avenue and Hands Across America--cassette tape (from box 9, folder 21) (Box 31)
  - Memories of forty years Great Flood of Greensville County--cassette tape, 1980 (from box 11, folder 20) (Box 31)
  - Steven-Price-Gibbson--cassette tape (from box 21, folder 17) (Box 31)
  - Sound effects--cassette tape (from box 21, folder 17) (Box 31)
  - Farewell Churchville High (from box 22, folder 8) (Box 31)
  - Margie Hevener Bird conversation/interview with Ginny Wrenn--cassette (2) tapes, 8 October 1996 (from box 25, folder 19) (Box 31)
  - Mary C. Wrenn--cassette tape (from box 27, folder 19) (Box 31)
  - Diaries (3 volumes), 1936-1938 (from box 10, folder 1) (Box 32)
  - Notes on the cruise of the USS Planter, 1944-1945 (from box 13, folder 12) (Box 32)
  - Watch Officer's Guide, 1941 (from box 13, folder 19) (Box 32)
  - American Cinematographer Hand Book and Reference Guide, 1950 (from box, folder ) (Box 32)
  - Richelieu Moss ledger, ca. 1907-1917 (from box 27, folder 25) (Box 32)
  - Bonsai scrapbook 1, 1972-1988 (from box 7, folder 18) (Box 33)
  - Visit of John Naka to Richmond Bonsai Society scrapbooks (2), 1988 (from box 7, folder 18) (Box 33)
  - Visit of John Naka and Richmond Bonsai Society Display at U.S. National Arboretum, Washington D.C., 1990 (from box 7, folder 18) (Box 34)
  - Richmond Bonsai Society and Dedication of Naka Pavilion at National Arboretum, 1990 (from box 7, folder 18) (Box 34)
  - Phi Kappa Sigma, Tau Chapter certificate, 25 February 1939 (from box 12, folder 11) (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Map of Okinawa and map of typhoons in Okinawa area, 1945 (from box 13, folders 26-27 ) (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Commission as aide-de-camp, 15 July 1980 (from box 15, folder 3) (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - Commission as aide-de-camp, 13 December 1982 (from box 15, folder 3) (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - Drawing of the USS Comte de Grasse (from box 15, folder 5) (Box 35, Folder 5)
  - Official Pictures in Color: a Century of Progress, 1934 (from box 21, folder 11) (Box 35, Folder 6)
  - Lady Sabena Club certificate, Sabena Belgian World Airlines, 14 June 1956 (from box 25, folder 20) (Box 35, Folder 7)
  - Confederate stock certificates, 1863 (from box 27, folder 28) (Box 35, Folder 8)
  - El Rodeo, University of Southern California yearbooks, 1941-1942 (from box 12, folder 19) (Box 36)
  - UFPA tie tacks, pins, and cuff links (from box 19, folder 6) (Box 37)
  - Jolly Wrenn Bards scrapbook, 1974-1991 (from box 23, folder 5) (Box 37)
  - Timepieces: Haiku Week-at-a-Glance, 1993 (from box 24, folder 4) (Box 38)
  - Photo scrapbook for article on flowers and gardening, 1980 (from box 24, folder 22) (Box 38)
  - Weddings and Flowers I've Planned scrapbook, 1977-1986 (from box 24, folder 23) (Box 38)
  - Richmond-on-the-James Richmond Showcase: Host's Handbook, 1981 (from box 25, folder 19) (Box 38)
  - International Society of Poets distinguished member certificate, 1996 (from box 23, folder 9) (Box 39)
  - International Society of Poets International Poet of Merit award plaque and medal, 1996 (from box 23, folder 9) (Box 39)
  - Mrs. Virginia and Mrs. America ribbons, 1956 (from box 25, folder 1) (Box 39)
  - Emporia scrapbook, 1938-1940 (from box 10, folder 5) (Box 40)
  - Mrs. Virginia scrapbook, 1956 (from box 25, folder 1) (Box 40)
  - The Artistry of Bonsai lecture and demonstration, 9 March 1985 (From box 7, folder 13) (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - Articles, 8 April 1987 (From box 8, folder 11) (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - Bonsai drawings--John Naka and Ginny Wrenn (From box 8, folder 11) (Box 41, Folder 3)
  - The Great Emporia Flood of 1940 article, 18 August 1980 (From box 11, folder 20) (Box 41, Folder 4)
  - Greensville County High School class of 1938 deceased members, 1988 (From box 12, folder 6) (Box 41, Folder 5)
  - Forest Hill Presbyterian Church certificate of appreciation, 2 November 1997 (From box 5, folder 3) (Box 41, Folder 6)
  - Maps of UFVA (UFPA, UFA) conferences, 1947-1997 (From box 19, folder 4) (Box 41, Folder 7)
  - Lake Page seasons photograph boards (From box 2, folder 16) (Box 42, Folder 1)
  - Crestwood Elementary School at Lake Page photoboard (From box 4, folder 17) (Box 42, Folder 2)
  - Bonsai photoboards (From box 8, folder 13) (Box 42, Folder 3)
  - Great Peanut Tour photoboard, ca. 2000s (From box 9, folder 2) (Box 42, Folder 4)
  - Ginny Wrenn Victorian Day banners and Victorian Day photoboard, ca. 1986-1989, 1997 (From box 7, folder 2) (Box 43, Folder 1)
  - Churchville High School images (From box 22, folder 8) (Box 43, Folder 2)
  - Winter scenes [Augusta County, Va.?] (From box 25, folder 22) (Box 43, Folder 3)